A Finding Aid to the Jimmy Hedges Papers and Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery Records, 1969-2016, bulk 1991-2013, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, 1985-2016; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 4.6 Linear feet Boxes 5-9, 31, 33, OV 32; 5.35 Gigabytes ER04-ER15
  - Herbert Singleton, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Julia Sisi, 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Lucille Smith, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Mary Tillman Smith, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Charles Stagg, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Sterling Strauser, 1994-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Vannoy Streeter, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - David Strickland, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Jimmie Lee Sudduth, circa 1993-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Johnnie Swearingen, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Stanley Szwarc, circa 1997-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Sarah May Taylor, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - James "Son" Thomas, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Annie Mural Tolliver, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Mose Tolliver, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - John Henry Toney, circa 1990s-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tom and Judy Touchstone, circa 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bill Traylor, 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Tago Trejo, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Eugene Von Bruckenheim, 2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Albert Wagner, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hubert Walters, 1997-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Gregory "Mr. Imagination" Warmack, 2008-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Derek Webster, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Dick and Maggie Wenstrup, circa 1999-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Myrtice West, circa 1994-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Charlie Willeto, circa 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Wallace Knox Wilkinson, 1985-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Purvis Young, 1990s-2006; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER14 (Box 8, Folder 15-16)
  - Purvis of Overtown, a film by David Raccuglia and Shaun Conrad, Digital Video Recording, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 3.16 Gigabytes Four computer files (Folder ER14)
  - Purvis Young, circa 1990s-2016; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 1-9)
  - Miscellaneous, A-Z, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
  - Artist Biographies Binder, circa 1900s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Artist Biographies Binder, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20-23)
  - Artist Biographies Binder, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24-26)
  - Artist Biographies Binder, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27-28)
  - Compiled Artist Biographies, 1990s; 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Quilts and Quilters, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - Oversize Howard Finster Document from Box 6, Folder 22, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 32)
  - Oversize Lonnie Holley Document from Box 6, Folder 36, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 32)
  - Artist Biographies, Digital Documents, 2004-2007; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes 15 computer files (Folder ER15)
- Collector and Gallery Files, 1992-2014; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 1.2 Linear feet Boxes 9-10
  Collector and gallery files document sales and consignments between Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery and private art collectors and art galleries. Files may include sale transaction documents, invoices, consignment and price lists, correspondence, and photographs of artwork.
  - American Artistry, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - American Primitive Gallery, 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Artisans Gallery, 1996-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Bebo Folk Art, 2000-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cotton Belt Gallery, 2007-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
  - Eileen West Gallery, 2007-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Galerie Bonheur, 2000-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Garde Rail Gallery, 1999-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Gordon Gallery, 2006-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Judith Racht Gallery, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Judy Saslow Gallery, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Koelsch Gallery, 1997-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Leslie Muth Gallery, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17-18)
  - Lyzones Gallery, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - North Shore Gallery, 1996-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Peligro Gallery, 1992-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21-24)
  - Shelton Gallery, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Timpson Creek Gallery, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Yard Dog Folk Art, 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
  - Collectors, A-J, 1997-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29-29)
  - Collectors, J-W, 1996-2014; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1-15)
- Exhibition and Art Fair Records, circa 1992-2013; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 10-11; 1.52 Gigabytes ER16-ER18
  Found here are files documenting Jimmy Hedges's participation in outsider and folk art fairs and the loan of artwork from the Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery to exhibitions. Of note are records of the "Intuit" art fair in Chicago, "Folk Fest" in Atlanta, and the "Outsider Art Fair" in New York. Files on these events may include brochures and programs, agreements and registration forms, sales records, lists of artwork, photographs, and digital materials. Additional photographs of events and art fairs are found in Series 8: Photographic Material.
  - "Antiques and Design in the Hamptons", 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - "Collect-O-Rama", 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - "Folk Fest", 1995-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18-19)
  - "Folk Fest", 2001; 2006-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20-23)
  - "Gramercy Park Antiques Show", 2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - "Intuit Show", 2002-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25-29)
  - "Marburger Farm Antique Show", 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - "Outsider Art Fair", 1996-2007; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER20 (Box 10, Folder 31-42)
  - "Outsider Art Fair", 2008-2010; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER16-ER18 (Box 11, Folder 1-9)
  - Jose Rivera at "Outsider Art Fair", Digital Photographs, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 0.011 Gigabytes 16 computer files (Folder ER16)
  - A Town...And Village Two, "Outsider Art Fair", film by Alice Bloom, Digital Video Recording, 2008; Archival Resource Key; 1.45 Gigabytes Three computer files (Folder ER17)
  - "Outsider Art Show", Digital Photographs, 2010; Archival Resource Key; 0.058 Gigabytes 28 computer files (Folder ER18)
  - "Outsider Art Fair" Programs, 1995-2010; 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 10-12)
  - "Outsiders Outside/Inside", 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "Pier Antiques Show", 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - "Pittsburg Folk Art" at Heinz History Center, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Stella Show Management, 2000-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee Aquarium Exhibition, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - "Triple Pier Antiques Show", 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Very Special Arts Gallery, "Contemporary Folk Art: A Five Year Retrospective", 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Art Fairs, Miscellaneous, 1990s-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 20-21)
- Regional Files, 1980s-2012; 1976; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 1.7 Linear feet Boxes 11-13
  Regional Files were created by Jimmy Hedges to document his travels throughout the United States to visit artists, art collectors, galleries, and attend art shows and events. Files primarily provide documentation by state and may include lists of contacts, notes, sales records, maps, brochures, correspondence, and photographs.
  - Alabama, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Arkansas, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - California, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Europe, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Florida, 1990s-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 26-29)
  - Georgia, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
  - Hamptons and Vermont, circa 2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Illinois (Chicago), circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 2-5)
  - Kentucky, 1990s; 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 6-7)
  - Louisiana, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
  - Michigan, 1995-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 10-12)
  - Mississippi, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - New Mexico, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - New York, 2000-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - North Carolina, circa 1985-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 17-20)
  - Ohio, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21-22)
  - Pennsylvania, Virginia, Washington, DC, 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Tennessee, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24-25)
  - Tennessee, 1990s-circa 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Texas, 1990s-2010; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 3-6)
  - Virginia and Carolinas, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
  - West Coast, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - West Virginia, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Printed Material, 1980-2013; Series 7; Archival Resource Key; 2.2 Linear feet Boxes 13-16, OV 32; 0.833 Gigabytes ER19
  Printed material includes annotated catalogs for the Slotin Folk Art Auction, as well as news clippings, magazines, newsletters, and exhibition catalogs, and announcements regarding Folk Art. Additionally there are a small number of Rising Fawn Folk Art Gallery brochures and postcards ar. One documentary in digital format, Visionary Voices of the South, and a vinyl sound recording of music by Borbetomagus and Shaking Ray Lewis are also found here.
  - Auction Catalog Pages, circa 1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Catalogs, Slotin Folk Art Auction, 1998-2009; 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 12-23)
  - Catalogs, Slotin Folk Art Auction, 2010-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
  - Clippings, General, circa 1990s-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6-9)
  - Clippings regarding Folk Art, 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10-13)
  - Visionary Voices of the South, Documentary, Digital Video Recording, 2011; Archival Resource Key; 0.833 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER19)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Hickory Museum of Art, 2005-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1980-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 16-21)
  - Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1985-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Gallery Brochures and Postcards, circa 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Journal, Envision, 1996-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Journals and Newsletters, 1985-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Magazines, 1991-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
  - Maps, 1982-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
  - Newsletter, "Folk Art Finder", 1993-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Postcards and Notecards (Blank), circa 1980s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Research Articles regarding Dellschau Books, 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1990s-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Published Recording by Borbetomagus and Shaking Ray Lewis, 1992; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound discs (vinyl) (Box OV 32)
- Photographic Material, circa 1990-2011; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; 7.9 Linear feet Boxes 16-30, 34-35; 7.79 Gigabytes ER20-ER35
  Photographic material includes thousands of color photographs, digital photographs, and a few slides taken by Jimmy Hedges to document his visits with artists, studios, works of art, exhibitions, art fairs, other events, and travel. Hedges visited the homes and studios of hundreds of outsider and folk artists and photographs of these visits include snapshots of Hedges with the artist, their work spaces, and individual works of art. Of note are extensive photographs of Georgia Blizzard, Howard Finster, Homer Green, Bessie Harvey, Danny Hoskinson, Paul Lancaster, A.J. Mohammed, Charlie Simmons, Jimmy Lee Sudduth, Mose Tolliver, and Purvis Young. Also found are several photograph albums containing photographs of multiple artists. The 2018 addition contains further material on Purvis Young.
  Photographs of events include several events and art fairs, including extensive documentation of the "Folk Fest" in Atlanta, "Intuit" art show in Chicago, and "Outsider Art Fair" in New York. Travel and personal photographs document Hedges's regional sightseeing, unidentified artist and art gallery visits, performances, and images of Lookout Mountain, Georgia.
  Photographs of Artists and Artwork are arranged alphabetically by name of artist, followed by photograph albums containing multiple artists, and photographs of artwork arranged alphabetically by subject. Event, travel, and personal photographs are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Artists and Artwork, circa 1990-2011; 8.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Jimmy Hedges, circa 1996-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1-10)
    - Jesse Aaron, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Minnie Adkins, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Leroy Alman, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Linda Anderson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Walter Anderson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - W.L. Anderson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Eddie Arnig, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Herbert Baggett, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 18-22)
    - Linvil Barker, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Leonard Belcher, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Mozelle Benson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - John Paul and Betty Blair, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Georgia Blizzard, circa 1994-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 27-39)
    - Georgia Blizzard, Digital Photograph, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.001 Gigabytes One computer file (Folder ER20)
    - Carl Block, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Wes Bobre, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Hawkins Bolin, circa 1997-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 42-44)
    - Rick Borg, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Loy Bowlin, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Jerry Brown, circa 2005; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital materials, see ER21 (Box 17, Folder 47-50)
    - Jerry Brown, Digital Photographs, 2006; Archival Resource Key; 0.021 Gigabytes 25 computer files (Folder ER21)
    - Richard Burnside, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 51-52)
    - Morgan Bush, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Ben Caldwell, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - H.R. Clark, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Annabelle Clayton, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Raymond Coins, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 57-60)
    - Jerry Coker, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Chuck Crosby, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Patrick Davis, circa 2009; Archival Resource Key; Includes born-digital records, see ER22 (Box 17, Folder 63-65)
    - Patrick Davis, Digital Photographs, 2009; Archival Resource Key; 0.03 Gigabytes 20 computer files (Folder ER22)
    - Burgess Delaney, circa 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 66-70)
    - Rev. H.D. Dennis, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Thornton Dial, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 72-73)
    - Brian Dowdall, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
    - Brian and Julie Dowdall, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    - Gerald "Creative" Dupree, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
    - Will Edmondson, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 11-12)
    - Willie Leroy Elliot, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Bud Ellis, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Minnie Evans, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Nora Ezell, circa 1998-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 16-21)
    - Roy Ferdinand, 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Howard Finster, circa 1990-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 23-36)
    - Howard and Roy Finster, circa 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 37-38)
    - Howard, Roy, and Michael Finster, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 39-40)
    - Sybil Gibson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Lee Godie, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - R.C. Gray, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Homer Green, circa 1991-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 44-61)
    - Mary Green, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Haint (Alan Wayne Bradley), 2009-2011; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 63-68)
    - Haint (Alan Wayne Bradley), undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
    - Barbara Hale, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
    - S. Hamman, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Anton Hardt, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Otesia Harper, circa 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 10-15)
    - Alyne Harris, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 16-18)
    - Bessie Harvey, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 19-31)
    - Alexandra Heller, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Lonnie Holley, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 33-59)
    - Lonnie Holley, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
    - Eric R. Holmes, circa 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 4-6)
    - Annie Hooper, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Danny Hoskinson, circa 1996-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 8-29)
    - Dorothy Hoskins, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Robert Howell, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 31-36)
    - L.V. Hull, circa 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 37-41)
    - Clementine Hunter, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Rev. J.L. Hunter, 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 43-44)
    - Alvin Janett, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - James Harold Jennings, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 46-47)
    - Willie Jinks, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 48-50)
    - Anderson Johnson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Daniel Johnson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 52-54)
    - "Mama" Johnson, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Clyde Jones, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - M.C. "5 cents" Jones, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Ray Jones, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - S.L. Jones, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Pat Kelly, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Elvin King, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Lee Kogan, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Paul Lancaster, circa 1995-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 7-15)
    - Bud Lee, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Billy Lemming, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Brenda Lemming Baty, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Willie Levoy, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Jr. Lewis, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Joe Light, circa 1990-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 21-31)
    - Joe and Rosie Lee Light, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 32-34)
    - Joe, Rosie Lee, and Rachel Light, circa 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Rosie Lee Light, 1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Calvin Livingston, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Ron Lockett, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 38-39)
    - Woodie Long, circa 1991-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 40-41)
    - Charlie Lucas, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 42-50)
    - David Lyons, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Makiki (Geraldo Alfonso), 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Jim Marbutt, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - L. Hog Mattingly, circa 1996-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 54-57)
    - Justin McCarthy, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Robert T. McKinney, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 59-60)
    - W.T. McLennon, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 61-62)
    - Clotee Mercier, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 63)
    - Mario Mesa, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 64)
    - Eric Miller, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 65)
    - R.A. Miller, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 66-68)
    - Sue Millon, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 69)
    - Reginald Mitchell, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 70)
    - A.J. Mohammed, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 71-78)
    - A.J. Mohammed, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - J.L. Nipper, circa 1992-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 3-6)
    - Isamu Noguchi, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Tom Ognoski, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - E.B. Ott, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - B.F. Perkins, circa 1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 10-12)
    - Dr. Regina Perry, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Virgil Perry, circa 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 14-15)
    - Frank Pickle, circa 1991-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 16-18)
    - B.O. Price, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 19)